Well, her comment is unimaginably stupid, offensive, and dangerous.
The raid she's talking about in Chicago was a brilliantly executed raid against a trained
Aragua complex filled with TDA terrorists.
It was one of the most successful law enforcement operations that we've seen in this country.
As you know, Laura, trained Aragua is responsible for some of the most gruesome, heinous crimes
that have occurred during the Biden administration.
Like the vicious sexual assault, kidnapping, and slaughter of Jocelyn Nungaree.
Or the stone-cold butchering of Lakin Riley.
And so these ICE officers, these heroes, saved God knows how many lives by getting these
TDA scum out of our country.
And protecting the lives, by the way, of every single person in that building.
A truly remarkable operation, Laura.
Stephen, Governor Pritzker is very upset that you all aren't going after the real problems.
Why?